Iinari Tatakentai! I want to be a righteous person!
Uwachira! Stargast on the road, Iinari and the chance for you two, please!
We are Chiba Nakane and Yoshida Pearl!
Please give us your best regards!
Today, it's these two!
Same age included, 19 years old!
Why are you showing off your age?
It's true, and I'm only 18.
I'm still on the verge.
I would like to ask you two a few questions.
Do you both like crepes?
Oh, I do!
You love them?
Yes, I do!
Do you eat them often?
What's that? You do eat it, don't you? Teenage girls like that.
Crepes...
But she went to eat with me the other day.
You want to eat with us?
Yes!
You like it that much?
I went to eat alone too.
Oh, yeah.
It's okay! Be proud!
It's not about being alone.
Don't worry!
Today, I'd like to introduce you two crepe lovers.
I'd like you two crepe lovers to explore.
Oh!
Aah!
What's that?
Cute.
Let's make our own crepes!
Sounds fun!
Today, I would like to invite you two to try your hand at making crepes.
There is a store called Romandroll on the first floor of E Beans.
We are going to visit there today.
We are going to visit them today and try our hand at making crepes.
It's amazing.
It's an exploration.
I'm so happy!
That's really great.
I'm so glad.
Try a little harder.
I'll do my best!
Now let's move on to the store.
Se-no!
Seino!
GO!
Hit it!
Okay, we've arrived at the store.
We're on the first floor of Ebbins.
Now, let's take a look at the menu.
You can see the menu outside.
There are a lot of menus.
There are so many kinds of food.
That's very tempting.
It's tempting.
Looks delicious.
Is there anything you want to eat?
I had this the other day.
It was really good.
But it wasn't too sweet.
It was so easy to eat.
I was able to eat it without hesitation.
Dokka dokka dokka
I'd have to say the ice cream rolls.
It's that summer.
I'm definitely craving ice cream right now.
Well, let's go inside.
Thank you for coming out.
It smells so good.
We'll be working with Mr. Watanabe and Ms. Isoda.
Mr. Watanabe and Ms. Isoda.
I'll be visiting you today.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm sorry for being so blunt.
Thank you very much.
When I said we'd start with you two...
You don't know what you're doing.
You don't know what to do.
So today, we're going to start with an example.
I'm going to show you a model.
And you're going to show us how to do it.
I'll show you what I'm going to do.
Okay.
Do you have any tips for making crepes?
What's the point?
I wonder.
Why not?
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
every time
Our image is that it would be difficult to fix the dough in a round shape.
Is that the point after all?
Yes, it is. The griddle is a high pitch. It has a high pitch, and I think the key is to cook the dough thinly there.
I see.
So, Mr. Watanabe, you are going to give us an example of how to do that.With that in mind, Mr. Watanabe once set the example.
Yes, let's do it.
The manager himself.
Manager, can't I fail at this?
First, let's start with the dough.
Yes, bake the dough first.
It smells really good.
It sure smells good.
This is it. This is it.
Wow, wow, wow.
It's so thin.
Wow, that was fast.
Oh, it looks difficult.
It is, isn't it?
Wow! It's in! It's in!
That's great!
Wow! It's like a cake shop!
Oh, on the outside?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my gosh!
Wow, Sui-chan, that's something!
Yeah, it's a decoration!
Amazing!
I was thinking of becoming a cake baker for a little girl.
Really?
Wow!
Oh, my gosh!
You're rocking it!
Oh, my God!
Oh!
That's how it's done! The way you roll it!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh!
That's great!
That's amazing!
Beautiful!
It's done!
Well then, Kaede-san, if you'll allow me to taste it...
Freshly made.
Is it okay?
Pow!
Freshly made!
Yes!
Bon appétit!
No need to say anything.
Wow, it's delicious!
Sticky but refreshing!
The cream is great too!
This is amazing!
I lost my vocabulary!
It's really delicious!
If this is an iron plate
If you put it in the middle first
I can see about half of these eyes
about this hiragana character.
Oh, I see.
And then, like this, it's like you're writing
Heh.
So, I'm going to turn it soon.
Up to the 10-minute mark on the clock.
I turn it to the 40-minute mark, turn it the other way, and finally, I draw the pattern, and that's it.
It's done!
Oh, good!
Oh!
Go again.
Ten minutes.
Forty minutes.
Go.
And three times.
Turn
And at the end
One more time
But...
Oh, okay.
Okay. Okay.
That's great.
Put down half of it.
I was just trying to put my body on.
From the brain.
Like this.
Oh, my God.
The joints are all set.
What's going on?
Wait a minute.
Like this.
Like a pencil.
Here we go.
Go for it!
Ow, ow, ow!
It hurts!
It's not falling anymore.
Laugh.
Like this.
It's different, isn't it?
Okay.
I see. Here.I see. Here.
I see.
Let's go with that.
Let's do it.
Let's go!
I can do it.
I can do it!
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going!
what the hell was that?
There's a weird turn.
please!
GO!
Sorry.
It's okay.
I'm scared.
Oh, Penn?
Pen!
What the hell!
And if you write "-" at the end...
And if I write the last one...
Come here!
It's okay, it's okay.
It smells so good.
What kind of applause is that?
No, of course not.
It's black. That's great.
Nice.
I'll have to try it.
Yeah, I'm sure you will.
Hey, you want to give him a try?
I'll give it a try.
Oh!
It's like ping-pong.
Oh, but it's great.
Yes, sir.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, now.
No, no, no, no.
Wait a minute.
There's a scuzzy part.
Mmm-hmm.
You're so good!
Careful, careful.
Okay, okay, okay, it's all cheesy and stringy.
Oh, but you're good.
It's hard.
We've both done a bit of dough.
I'm not sure if it's tasteful.
I don't know.
But I've never seen anyone do it so well the first time.
It's amazing that you didn't get stuck.
Thank you very much.
You're a great manager!
I have to tell my part-timers like this at first.
I have to make sure they don't quit.
Thank you very much!
I've only done it once.
Shall we go for the real thing?
That's okay.
No matter how it goes next time, we'll do it all the way to the end.
Let's do it.
Let's go for the real thing.
Let's go for the real thing, Shinjuku.
I'll do my best.
Let's do it together!
Don't worry. Don't move your legs.
I like it!
All right, all right, all right!
Here we go! Go!
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful!
I like strawberries, so I'll put strawberries.
Okay, I put strawberries. Thank you very much.
Arrange them like this, in a triangle.
Triangle. Triangle.
Like this.
Oh!
You're cooking today.
No, no, no, no.
I'm just putting the strawberries on the table.
Yummy.
Ooh! Thank you!
Cute! Cute!
It looks like a face! Look at that!
One bite!
With fangs!
Like this!
Ooh!
Like this?
Here you go!
Laughs.
A little something else.
What's that? If you want to add a topping or something...
Like piklis.
Chocolate chips, corn flakes...
That's great!Great!
Oh, my God!
You don't think so?
Let's do it with corn flakes!
Yes!
Oh, man! I have a crepe just the way I like it!
Everyone knows! My favorite!
They know!
Yes!
Wow!
Looks delicious!
It's done!
Shinjuku Rape!
It's like wrapping it, right?
Shall I take it off?
LOL!
I'll do my best!
What is this?
What is this lump? Cheese bread.
Ta-da!
My first crepe!
I love it!
What do you think? Manager.
It's so cute!
Manager!
You should make him feel better!
Wrapping it in paper makes it look better.
Yes, it does!
What do you think?
Ta-da!
It's done!
Wow!
That's great!
What's your name?
Shinjuku Red.
I don't care what's in it!
That was strong!
Pass the baton!
Cute!
Let's go next!
Oh, wow!
That's great!
Oh!
That's a little bit!
Good!
The real powerhouse type!
That's great!
That was totally good!
Oh!
Ooh!
Oh, my God! That's great! Rapid growth!
You taught me how to do that! It's spinning at the wrist!
Yes, it is! That's great!
Thank you! I couldn't decide on the indirect!
What should I do inside?
I wanted to do something Japanese, and I like Lennymo Tart, so Lennymo Tart style!
I see! Like a purple sweet potato roll.
Yes! Leave it!
Put this in too! Yes! Okay!
Do you make it like carotene?
Wow! Wow!
Ah! Carotene!
So that's how it comes out! Wow! That's amazing!
I mean, look! Oh! It's true!
She's just like a little girl! So cute!
So cute!
Oh!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God! Is it over? Is it over?
Is it over? So sweet!
Gentle!
Yes! That's great!
And there's a purple sweet potato in the middle!
Oh, wow! Is this it? Yes!
Oh, wow! Good!
Good!
That's great! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Oh, my God!
Like this!
That's so great!
One piece
Crumble it up
Spread it on the bean paste.
Like this.
Oh!
Ooh!
Yeah!
I'm on it, I'm on it!
I'm impressed!
Oh, my gosh!
That's great!Wow!
Here, give me that!
Oh!
I'll make this one last time.
Please!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's okay, it's okay.
You'll get it in the edit.
It's done!
Karen Montblanc.
Karen Montblanc!
She put her name on it.
Looks delicious!
Amazing!
At the eat-in corner.
So stylish!
Now that you're here, let's try some of the crepes we made.
Let's sample the crepes we made!
Let's start with
Sindhu Crepe.
Let's start with the appearance.
Cute!
Sindhu Crepe is kind of hard to eat.
But it's known for its deliciousness.
Because they have a reputation for being delicious.
And this one, too.
I ripped it so weird!
It's okay. It's okay.
May I have a word?
It's black!
It's all black.
It's so obvious.
Oh, my God.
You made it yourself.
[Hajime Shacho's ending]
It's easy to spill. I eat it normally.
It's easy to spill.
I'd like you to eat it with care.
Oh, it's delicious.
Can you tell them how it tastes?
It tastes like chocolate.
Chocolate is helping me.
Why do you say it's helping me so much?
But it also tastes bitter.
But it also tastes sweet, so it's like a plus-minus zero.
Can you say something positive?
Can I have a plus?
It's delicious.
The ingredients helped me.
The ingredient wachal world.
Now all we have to do is polish it up.
You've done it the first time.
Amazing.
If you look closely, you can see the strawberries sticking out of the sides.
It's a picture I've never seen on a crepe before.
Is this your personality?
It is individuality, isn't it?
It's delicious.
Curry Mont Blanc from Shinji Crepe.
Next.
Curry Mont Blanc.
Why do you put your name on it?
It's the one that's not on the menu.
We made it for you.
Original.
We discussed the order.
It has two kinds of red potatoes inside.
Two layers.
Autumn taste convenience store.
Autumn Taste Convenience Store.
What a name!
Why did you ask back?
You know what I mean.
Bon appétit.
Wow, it looks delicious!
Delicious.
Looks delicious.
Looks delicious
Yummy.
Wait a minute, rerun.
I really saw it again just now.
It's really good!
I wonder what it is.
It's not particularly fiery.
I don't know.
Because I grilled it.
Maybe...
Maybe it's burnt.
That's right.
I thought it might be burnt.
But I didn't. It was like I was eating the real thing.
It's delicious!
It's amazing!
I was so surprised!
Double Mont Blanc
Surprisingly...
It wouldn't be surprising if it was on the menuI wouldn't be surprised if it was on the menu.
It feels right, doesn't it?
You could do curry clips.
No, no, no, wait a minute.
Don't be so irresponsible.
It would be a grown-up move.
Shinchi Crepe
Shinchi Crepe is a bit...
How about it?
Please
Delicious!
I'm glad you like it.
The fact that you made it yourself...
I think it's a combination of the fact that I made it myself.
This is delicious.
It's so good.
Thank you for watching.
Now that we've finished the tasting...
It was delicious.
Since this was such a valuable experience for us.
Let's say thank you for such a precious experience.
Thank you very much for today's experience.
Thank you very much.
I think I want to come here again from now on!
It's really delicious!
The crepe batter is delicious.
but the ingredients and everything else is delicious as well.
I hope you all will have a chance to come and try them.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
Just so you know... I asked the manager about the two crepes and...
How was it?
We had a great time.
And most of all, they were amazingly good.
Really?
Yes, I'm sure.
But it was a lot of fun meeting you guys.
Thank you very much.
If there's anything I can do, any surprises & collaborations, if there are any...
If you don't mind.
I'd really appreciate it.
Thank you very much.
So, today's crepe making experience
Thank you very much for this truly valuable experience!
Thank you very much.
Romandroll, located on the first floor of eBeans
We have a lot of really great crepes to choose from.
Please come and visit us!
They also have an Instagram page, so please check it out!
Please check it out!
Thank you very much for your time today!
Bye bye!
It's been a fun place to work.
Thank you very much.